<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cv on sv@work</title>
    <link>https://svatwork.github.io/tags/cv/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cv on sv@work</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 11:18:25 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://svatwork.github.io/tags/cv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Crossover Interview</title>
      <link>https://svatwork.github.io/posts/my-crossover-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 11:18:25 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://svatwork.github.io/posts/my-crossover-interview/</guid>
      <description>I applied to CrossOver last month. They have an automated interview process, where you have to pass a list of tests like basic cognitive aptitude and language skills.
It seemed like I passed all of the tests, however, after submitting my final test I heard that my score wasn&amp;rsquo;t sufficient to become a Product Knowledge Curator to earn that sweet American salary of $100K a year.
My final test consisted of creating three product knowledge articles based on customer inquiries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts On The CNCF CKA Exam After Passing With 93%</title>
      <link>https://svatwork.github.io/posts/cka-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 15:45:25 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://svatwork.github.io/posts/cka-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Last month I passed the CNCF CKA exam. I&amp;rsquo;ve been postponing the exam date for the better part of the year, assuming that it would be a very difficult exam. From what I&amp;rsquo;ve read, it used to be a difficult exam up until they broke the exam into two parts: CKA and CKAD. This happened around two years ago.
The CKA is supposed to be the more difficult one of the two exams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Lessons Did I Learn In My Career So Far</title>
      <link>https://svatwork.github.io/posts/career-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 13:22:10 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://svatwork.github.io/posts/career-lessons/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve started doing freelance cloud engineering since the end of 2018. During software engineering at my first full-time employer, I was invited to work on a start-up. At one point the money ran out, so I went to look for a new employer in 2019. There, I worked on system administration during the time DevOps and Cloud were becoming trending.
I took a break for a while to travel, and had some time to think about what direction to head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yet Another CKA Study Guide</title>
      <link>https://svatwork.github.io/posts/yet-another-cka-study-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 12:46:08 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://svatwork.github.io/posts/yet-another-cka-study-guide/</guid>
      <description>As of March 2020 there are loads of resources to study for CKA (Certified Kubernetes Administrator). A lot of people have compiled their tips and tricks, created exercise repositories and applications, compiled yet more lists of additional resources, etc.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to contribute by sharing my resource list. This is not my original work, and you will find all sources in the &amp;ldquo;Source index&amp;rdquo; paragraph. I&amp;rsquo;ve scheduled the test for next month and I&amp;rsquo;ll report later to share my own opinion about the test, if there&amp;rsquo;s anything I can contribute.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>