<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>experience on sv@work</title>
    <link>https://www.svatwork.com/tags/experience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in experience on sv@work</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 11:18:25 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.svatwork.com/tags/experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Crossover Interview</title>
      <link>https://www.svatwork.com/posts/my-crossover-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 11:18:25 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.svatwork.com/posts/my-crossover-interview/</guid>
      <description>I applied to CrossOver last month. They have an automated interview process, where you have to pass a list of tests like basic cognitive aptitude and language skills.
It seemed like I passed all of the tests, however, after submitting my final test I heard that my score wasn&amp;rsquo;t sufficient to become a Product Knowledge Curator to earn that sweet American salary of $100K a year.
My final test consisted of creating three product knowledge articles based on customer inquiries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Lessons Did I Learn In My Career So Far</title>
      <link>https://www.svatwork.com/posts/career-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 13:22:10 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.svatwork.com/posts/career-lessons/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve started doing freelance cloud engineering since the end of 2018. During software engineering at my first full-time employer, I was invited to work on a start-up. At one point the money ran out, so I went to look for a new employer in 2019. There, I worked on system administration during the time DevOps and Cloud were becoming trending.
I took a break for a while to travel, and had some time to think about what direction to head.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>